name: 'Adverbs of Frequency'
questions:
  -
    question: 'I $ coffee after dinner.'
    answers:
      - 'never don''t drink'
      - 'never drink'
      - 'don''t never drink'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'My husband $.'
    answers:
      - 'makes sometimes dinner'
      - 'dinner makes sometimes'
      - 'sometimes makes dinner'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'I $ in the morning.'
    answers:
      - 'always take a shower'
      - 'take always a shower'
      - 'always a shower take'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'The restaurant $.'
    answers:
      - 'closes usually late'
      - 'closes late usually'
      - 'usually closes late'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'She $ at home.'
    answers:
      - 'usually has breakfast'
      - 'has usually breakfast'
      - 'has breakfast usually'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'We $ for dinner.'
    answers:
      - 'have sometimes pizza'
      - 'sometimes have pizza'
      - 'have pizza sometimes'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'She $ after work.'
    answers:
      - 'never doesn''t go shopping'
      - 'never goes shopping'
      - 'goes never shopping'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'My mom $ early.'
    answers:
      - 'gets up always'
      - 'gets always up'
      - 'always gets up'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'Spanish people $ at home.'
    answers:
      - 'have usually lunch'
      - 'usually have lunch'
      - 'have lunch usually'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: '$ at work'
    answers:
      - 'I never speak English'
      - 'I never don''t speak English'
      - 'Naver I don''t speak English'
    correct: 1
